http://www.abmp.com/privacy-policy

Last Modified: November 26, 2018
Professional Assist Corporation, DBA Associated Bodywork & Massage Professionals, and including subsidiaries Associated Skin Care Professionals, Associated Hair Professionals, and Associated Nail Professionals (collectively "ABMP," “we,” “our,” “us”) recognizes the significance and importance of your information and online security and is committed to ensuring the information you share on our website is handled carefully and with consideration. To that end, we have created the following Privacy Policy that describes how we collect, use, disclose, and secure the information that you share with us when you use our website or services (collectively, the “Services”).
What Information Do We Collect?
We may collect personal information about you, meaning information that can uniquely identify you, from various sources, such as:
Directly from you when you use the Services, such as when you register for an account, access certain features or content, or order products; and
From our subsidiaries, affiliates, service providers, business partners, and other third parties.
The personal information we may collect about you may include, without limitation:
Contact information, such as name, postal address, email address, phone number, and website;
Demographic information, such as age and job information;
Login information, such as username and password;
Proof of training and state licensing/registration credentials; and
Payment and financial details, such as payment card number, expiration date, authentication code, billing address, and bank account number.
When you use the Services, we may also collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. We may also use third-party analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) that collect information about use of the Services and user traffic. The information we may collect by automated means may include, without limitation:
Information about the devices you use to access the Services (such as the IP address and the type of the device, operating system, and web browser);
Dates, times, and duration of use of the Services (including whether you are a repeat or first-time visitor); and
Information on actions taken when using the Services (such as page views and website navigation patterns).
This information helps us to improve and personalize our Services, including by enabling us to identify and authenticate members. To the extent that we associate it with personal information, we will treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
How is the Information Used?
We may use information we obtain about you to:
Process orders you place and complete other transactions you have requested using the Services, and provide you with products and services you request;
Send you information or materials you request;
Maintain a record of your purchases and other transactions using the Services;
Respond to your questions and comments and provide customer support;
Communicate with you about our products, services, offers, and promotions;
Operate, evaluate, and improve our business and the products and services we offer;
Analyze and enhance our marketing communications and strategies;
Analyze trends and statistics regarding use of the Services and transactions conducted using the Services;
Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims, and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users;
Enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements; and
Comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards.
We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
How is the Information Disclosed?
We may disclose aggregated information about our members, and information that does not identify any individual member, without restriction. We may disclose personal information about you:
To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements;
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of ABMP, our members, or others; and
With your consent.
We also reserve the right to transfer your personal information to a buyer or other transferee in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale, or other transfer of some or all of our assets.  Should such a sale, merger, or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.
How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals
Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow the collection of information about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services. At this time, the Services do not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding such collection of your information, and the Services may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.
How Secure is the Visitor Information?
To safeguard your personal information when engaging in monetary transactions, we use Transport Layer Security (TLS) software, which encrypts information you input. This is designated in your browser address field by "https" and a padlock icon at the bottom right of each page. We have implemented measures intended to protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Please note that the electronic transmission of information is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place to safeguard personal information will never be defeated or fail, or that such measures will always be sufficient or effective. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.
Accessing and Changing your Information
You can review and change the personal information associated with your account by logging into your account and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at expectmore@abmp.com to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.
Your Rights
We offer you the following choices about the information we collect from you and how we communicate with you:
Cookies
Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features of the Services.
Promotional Communications
If you do not want us to use your contact information to promote our own products or services, you can opt out by logging into your account and adjusting your member preferences in your account profile or by sending us an email stating your request to expectmore@abmp.com. If you have received a promotional email from us, you can also opt out of receiving future promotional emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in such email.
Web Analytics
You may opt out of the aggregation and analysis of data collected about you on the Services by Google Analytics by installing the Google browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Children Under Age 13
The Services are not directed to, and ABMP does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at expectmore@abmp.com.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
ABMP reserves the right to update or change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to our Privacy Policy, we will provide notice to you (by email and/or posting on the Services) that our privacy practices have changed and will provide a link to the new policy. In the event we make a material change to how we use your personal information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date this Privacy Policy was last modified is at the top of this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for any updates or changes.
Data Transfers
ABMP is based in the State of Colorado in the United States. When we obtain information about you, we may transfer, process, and store such information outside of the country in which you reside, including in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the transfer to and processing and storage of your information in countries outside of your country of residence, which may have different data protection laws than those in the country where you reside.
Questions and Comments
The Services are operated by Associated Bodywork & Massage Professionals, Inc., 25188 Genesee Trail Road, Suite 200, Golden, Colorado 80401.
All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to the Services should be directed to: expectmore@abmp.com.
Practitioners
Students
Educators
Employers
Public
ABMP Members
Join Now!
Learn more about ABMP membership
ABMP Member Reviews:
Trustpilot
Please note: We have recently updated our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Learn more...Continue
